(Sheldon(inside):)Take the hint, Stuart.
The lady said good night.
(Amy:)How did you get into my apartment?
Wow. Ls that the kind of nagging
I can expect now that you're my girIfriend?
(Sheldon:)Good thing I drew this up.
(Amy:)What's that?
(Sheldon:)I present to you
the relationship agreement.
(Sheldon:)A binding covenant that, in its 31 pages,
enumerates, iterates and codifies...
(Sheldon:)...the rights and responsibilities
of Sheldon Lee Cooper...
(Sheldon:)...here and after known as
"the boyfriend"...
(Sheldon:)...and Amy Farrah Fowler,
here and after known as "the girIfriend."
(Amy:)It's so romantic.
(Sheldon:)Mutual indemnification always is.
(Sheldon:)Why don't you start perusing
while I set up my notary stamp.
"Section 5: Hand-holding.